Ah, hello
あ、どうも
Thank you.
どう も
nice to meet you.
初めまして
This is Kitajima, the president.
社長の北島です
Is it Reina-chan?
レイナちゃんだっけ?
Oh, Reina-chan, please sit down.
あ、レイナちゃん、座っておいてください
I'm going to have an interview right now.
ちょっと今から面接していくんですけど、
To make a point about whether or not you heard this story during the interview.
面接時にこの話聞いたとか聞いてないとかの水かけ論をつくために
I'm rotating the camera on purpose,
わ ざとカメラ回してるんですけど、
Is it okay if I understand that?
それだけご了承いただいてもいいですか?
yes.
はい
thank you.
ありがとうございます
It's so cute.
めっちゃ可愛いね
99 years old.
99歳
It's too cute, isn't it?
可愛すぎでしょ
It's okay, there's no video of this.
大丈夫、これ映像出ないから
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Right away, please write your name at the registration office of this company.
早速なんですけど、このコンパニーの登録所にお名前とか書いて
Can I have it?
いただ いてもいいですか?
yes.
はい
I'm afraid to write, so is it okay?
書くの怖いんで、ねえなんだけど大丈夫ですか?
Are you scared?
怖いの?
it's okay.
大丈夫だよ
What are you scared of?
なに怖いの?
I can't see it.
見割れ
picture?
え?
Can't see it?
見割れ?
I don't and it's okay.
しないし大丈夫だよ
Are you okay.
大丈夫
That's fine, for now.
まあまあいいよ、とりあえず
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Is there anyone asking?
聞かれる人がいるの?
No.
ないです
Even though it's this cute?
こんな可愛いのに?
A 19 year old is definitely a college student.
19歳って絶対大学生だよね
Did you come every morning because it was summer vacation?
夏休みだから毎朝来ちゃったの?
yes.
はい
That's right.
そうなんだ
Would you like to write down your address as well?
住所も書きますか?
Write your address.
住所書いて
Where are you from?
どこから来たの?
Shiga prefecture.
滋賀県です
滋賀県
I came because I came all the way.
わざわざ来たから来たの
It's really far away.
めっちゃ遠いじゃん
How many centimeters tall are you?
身 長何センチあるの?
It is 160 cm.
160センチです
It's normal.
普通だね
yes.
はい
How many cups does this have?
これ何カップあるの?
I'm an F cup.
Fカップです
F cup?
Fカップ?
That's popular.
モテモテじゃん、それ
That's amazing.
すごいね
Show me from the side, please.
横から見せてよ、ちょっと
That's amazing.
すごいね
I like the style.
スタイルいいね
No, no, I'm sorry.
いやいや、ごめんね
It's so boring.
めっちゃつまらなくて
It's okay because I'll check it at the start.
スタートで確認するから大丈夫
Shit, thank you.
くそ、ありがとう
Don't you have a boyfriend?
彼氏いないんだっけ?
This is what everyone has heard,
これみんな聞いてることだけどさ、
How many people have experience?
経験人数何人くらいだ?
経験人数?
About 5 people.
5人くらい
About 2 people?
2人くらい?
About 5 people.
5人くらい
5 people at 19 years old.
19歳で5人
You're playing around a lot.
結構遊んでるね
That's right.
そうなんだ
Are all five of these people dating?
この5人は全員付き合ってる人?
You're such a playboy, you're such a mess.
遊び人じゃん、めちゃくちゃ
That's right.
そうなんだ
Why do you want to do this kind of work?
どうしてこんなお仕事しようと思う?
I wanted to decide on the money.
金を決めたくて
Ah, I want to decide on the money.
あ、お金を決めたくて
He's 19 years old and solid.
19歳で堅実なんだね
My mom is in debt so I can't buy alcohol at all.
うちのお酒なんか借金まくるマミで全然買えないよ
Really.
本当に
The day after payday, the president said,
給料日の次の日には社長すいません、
I'll ask you to lend me some money.
お金貸してくださいなんて言っちゃうんだよ
You can't see the alcohol.
見られないお酒、お前
Really.
本当に
It's cute, really.
かわいいね、本当
Nothing but cuteness comes out.
かわいいしか出てこないよ
Let me add some color.
ちょっと色を取らせてね
There's nothing special though.
別に何もないけど
It's cute.
かわいいじゃん
By the way, do you have any experience in delivery health?
ちなみにデリヘルの経験ってある?
No.
ないです
Not at all?
全くない?
Don't you have anything to worry about?
なんか心配事とかない?
What are you most worried about?
一番心配のこと何がある?
I have to find out.
バレないと
Will you find out?
バレない?
I won't find out, I won't find out.
バレない、バレない
It's absolutely fine.
絶対大丈夫だよ
If I found out that much, it would be a social climate and I would pack up everything.
そんなにバレてたら世の中風土くて全部詰めちゃうよ
That's what it is.
そういうもんだよ
After all, he is the one who started our shop.
う ちのお店やっぱり始めてる子だからさ、
I basically give classes, but
基本的に講習っていうのも行ってるんだけど、
Do you understand what a lecture is?
講習ってわかるかな?
What is the course?
講習って何ですか?
The course was taught by my husband, Kozaki.
講習っていうのは、うちのこの主人の小崎が、
From the beginning, we teach people how to respond to sweets with their bodies.
一からね、お菓子さんへの対応の仕方とかを体で教えるってこと
in.
で
And then, I have to check my armpit hair after all.
そして さ、やっぱり脇毛チェックとかもしなきゃいけないから
difference.
さ
Isn't it good?
いい じゃない?
If you put in unnecessary hair, it's sweets, because our store is a high-end store.
無駄毛とか入れたらお菓子さん、うちの店高級店だからさ
The F cup I mentioned earlier might also be a lie.
さっきのFカップってのも嘘かもしれないじゃん
Actually, it might only be C or C.
本当はCかCしかないかもしれないでしょ
Yeah.
うん
I'll check that too.
それも確認するから
Got it.
分かった
yes.
はい
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Yeah.
うん
Well, let's check it out.
じゃあ、確認していこうか
じゃあ、チェックしておこうか
It's okay, it's okay.
大丈夫、大丈夫
How many cups did you just say?
さっき何カップって言ったの?
I'm an F cup.
Fカップです
copper?
どう?
There seems to be an F recently.
最近Fがありそう
There's an F.
Fがありますね
Wow, that's amazing.
えー、すごいね
Just look for me.
ちょっと俺の探して
It's okay if you check.
チェックだったら大丈夫
That's amazing.
すごいね
Give it a little stab.
ちょっとツンツン刺してみ
Give me a hand check too.
ハンドチェックもあげて
This is okay now, this.
これはもう大丈夫だよ、これ
What happened?
どうしちゃったの?
what happened?
どう したの?
Take off, take off.
脱ぐ、脱ぐ
脱 ぐ、 脱ぐ
I checked incorrectly earlier.
さっきチェックが違ったじゃん
I can't see if she's wearing underwear.
下着つけてるか見えない
I have to check my underwear and the color of my dick.
下着もチェックして、チクビの色も確認しなきゃ
It's really good.
めちゃくちゃいいじゃん
Please come a little closer.
ちょっと寄してごらん
amazing
すごい
hey.
ね
OK?
大丈夫 ですか?
I have to check everything.
全部チェックしないと
Take off your top clothes.
上の服脱いじゃん
I'll take it off.
脱ぐよ
Please share it.
分け上げてごらん
No, no.
いや、いや
I have to raise it.
上げないと
I have to check it out.
チェックしなきゃ
Let me show you.
見せてごらん
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
大丈夫、大丈夫、大丈夫
it's okay.
大丈夫だよ
Here, let me show you.
ほら、見せてごらん
Now to the world.
さあ、世界に
Osaki, this new Aino check is also important.
大崎、これニューアイノチェックも大事だから
No, I don't like it.
いや、嫌です
Really.
本当に
It would be no good if the customer had a bad experience later.
お客さん、後で嫌な思いをしてたらダメだから
Let me show you the opposite.
反対に見せてごらん
Because it's a joke.
冗談だから
What if the customer asks you to push it aside later?
お客さんが後で脇に押してって言ったらどうするの?
No, I don't like it.
いや、嫌です
It's no good, I have to let it go.
ダメだよ、寄せなきゃ
Because we have all kinds of perverted customers.
いろんな変態のお客さんいるんだから
As much as possible, there is little use for customers.
できるだけお客さんの用途はだいぶないし
It's really cute, though.
めっちゃかわいいね、しかし
Come over here and take a look.
こっちおいでごらん
Shall I take off my underwear too?
下も脱いじゃおうか
Look at that butt over there.
向こう、お尻も見てごらん
Look at your butt.
お尻抜けてごらん
Don't hide it.
隠しちゃダメじゃん
Please show me properly.
ちゃんと見せてごらん
Ah, that's good.
ああ、いいじゃん
Her butt is jiggling too.
ぷるんぷるんじゃん、お尻も
It's a beautiful shape.
綺麗な形してるね
Customers, don't worry about this.
お客さん、おろこぶれよ、これ
Take a moment to get your hands on it.
ちょっと、そこに手ついてごらん
Yes, stick your butt out.
そう、お尻突き出してごらん
That's fine.
いいじゃん
What do you think, Shirari?
どうよ、しらり
nice.
いいね
No, it's okay, a lot.
いや、大丈夫、たくさん
Don't hide it.
隠しちゃダメだよ
There's no negotiation if you hide it.
隠しちゃ交渉はないからね
I see.
そっか
I'm also very aware of my underwear.
下着もちゃんと気づかってるんで
Let me expand it a little.
ちょっと、広げてもらおう
That's fine.
いいじゃん
Shall we check out the mango?
マンゴーチェックしよっか
picture?
え?
I'll check everything,
全部チェックするよ、
Today is.
今日は
It's necessary to check the count.
カ ウントチェックとか必要だからね
Around here.
この辺とか
Drink alcohol, just in case.
お酒、仮にやって
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
I have to look at the customers.
俺、お客さんの方見なきゃ
Treat alcohol as if you were a customer.
お酒、お客さんと思って対応して
Tell me what feels good.
どこが気持ちいいか、俺、言ってごらん
Where does it feel good?
どこが気持ちいいか
I'll do it.
俺、やってやるよ
I have to check everything.
全部チェックしないといけないからさ
Yeah.
うん
You're doing something beautiful.
綺麗なことしてるね
Okay, it's mango.
いいよ、マンゴーしてるじゃん
Stick it out more.
もっと突き出して
sorry.
すみません
Let's check out more bread.
もっとパンチェックしようぜ
hey.
ね
This isn't public.
これ、公衆じゃないもんね
Let's go public properly.
ちゃんと公衆しよう
If you don't hide it, you'll be embarrassed.
隠さなきゃお客さん、恥ずかしいでしょ
Wow, that's good.
うわ、いいじゃん
It's cute.
かわいいね
Which one do you want?
どっちにもんだほしい?
Kozaki or Yoshinari?
小崎か吉成か
I don't like either.
どっちも嫌です
Well, I drink both.
まあ、どっちも飲んでるんだけどね
no.
いや
Well then, let me have a drink first, Kozaki.
じゃあ、まず小崎から飲んでもらおうか
I'll have Kosaki drink it.
小崎に飲んでもらうよ
Lean over there.
そっちにもんたれかがって
Have more drinks with your customers.
お客さんともっと飲んでもらうのよ
yes.
はい
I have to get it out properly now.
今、ちゃんと出せなきゃ
So what happened?
じゃあ、どうしちゃったの?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
It's not like this yet.
まだこんなもんじゃないよ
Hey, aren't you getting bigger?
なんか、こりぃ、大きくなってない?
this.
これ
It will swell up really well.
めっちゃ、ぷっくり膨らんできますね
It feels good.
気持ちいいね
It's getting really big.
すごく大きくなってる
Have you been touched by your past boyfriends?
歴代の彼氏たちに触られてきたの?
Hey, what's going on?
なあ、どうなの?
I was touched.
触られてちゃった
Which one is you, the past boyfriend or the one behind you?
歴代の彼と後ろにどっちがお前?
I don't know yet.
まだわかんないね
Well then, get serious, you.
よっしゃ、本気出してやれ、お前
If it's bad, please let me know.
下手くそだったら教えてね
Does it feel good?
気 持ちいい?
気持ちいい?
It's cute.
かわいいね
Looks like we'll be living together for the first time in a while.
近ぶりの暮らしちゃそうだね
I love it so much.
すーげー好き
I really like it.
めっちゃ好きなんだ
When was the last time?
最後、いつでした?
About a month.
1ヶ月ぐらい
It's piling up, that's it.
溜まってるじゃん、それじゃん
You look happy.
嬉しそうだね
She's so cute but she's such a pervert?
こんなかわいいのにこんな変態なの?
That's dangerous.
やばいじゃん
I took the parts off.
パーツ脱がしたんだ
It's so wet.
びっちょびっちょぶじゃん
What happened?
どうしちゃったの?
hot.
熱い
This is sure to be popular with customers.
絶対お客さん人気出るよ、これ
It's style.
スタイルすんじゃん
Let's try it again.
もう一回やってあげよう
I'll make your drink colder.
お酒もっと冷めてあげる
You want them both to cool down, right?
両方冷めてほしいでしょ、近ぶり
Tell me how you feel about being treated.
どんな風にされた気持ちか、言ってあげて
What more?
もっと何?
Do you want it to be stronger?
もっと強くしてほしいの?
Does it really feel good?
本当に気持ちいいの?
That's it.
そんな
I can do it.
あんまできる
Does it smell like salt?
塩とかこいちゃう?
There were quite a few.
あんまあったもんね
You're getting stronger.
強がってきますね
Okay, did you call me?
よいしょね、電話あってあげたの?
What's going on? Did you call me?
どうなっちゃうの、電話あってあげたの?
What will happen?
どうなっちゃう?
copper?
どう?
fun?
楽しみ?
Isn't it good?
いいでしょ?
good?
いい?
Isn't it nice to be like this?
こうやってあってあげるのいいんじゃない?
Really.
めっちゃ
Messed up.
めちゃめちゃ
Is it no good?
ダメなの?
stop?
やめる?
Do you want me to continue?
続けてほしい?
Then tell me to continue.
じゃあ続けてって言って
Well, let me give you all my legs.
じゃあ足も全部あげちゃおうか
Look, this room is by myself.
こっちの部屋だってほら、自分で
Turn it from my side.
うち側から手回してほら
Okay, okay.
よしよし
I received a phone call while doing peace.
ピースしながら電話あってもらった
Look, both of you should make a piece with both hands.
ほ ら、両方ちゃんと両手でピースして
Turn it from my side.
うち側から手回して
Then I can't help it.
じゃあこうしょうがないよ
What happened to me that it felt so good?
どうしちゃったの、そんな 気持ちよくなっちゃって
Look here.
こっち見てほら
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?
stop?
やめる?
continue?
続ける?
What should I do?
どうする?
No more?
もうダメ?
If I'm told no, I'll say no.
ダメって言われたら、あれちゃうって言っちゃうよ
I'm on the phone, but I'll be right away.
電話だけどすぐいっちゃうの
give?
あげる?
this is?
これは?
Where does it feel good?
どこが気持ちいいの?
ど こ が気持ちいいの?
Where does it feel good?
どこが気持ちいいの?
How much is this?
これ くらい?
No?
ダメ?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
気持ちいい?
terrible?
やばい?
Can you have it all?
全部持ってくれる?
Yeah.
うん
What kind of bad?
どういうダメ?
Don't you want a penis?
おちんこ欲しいダメ?
Did you want it?
欲しくなっちゃったの?
Does it feel too good?
気持ちよすぎる?
terrible.
やばい
Are you really wet?
めっちゃ濡れてるんちゃう?
Doesn't it feel good?
気持ちよくない?
Are you wet?
濡れてるの?
With both hands, let's do it from our side.
両方のこっちの手でも うち側からクパーしてほら
Peace and see.
ピースしてほら
Peace.
ピ ース
Look this way.
こっち向いてほら
Shall I spread this photo around?
この写真ばらまいちゃおうか
Just kidding.
冗談だよ
There are bad adults like that.
そういう悪い大人がいるからね
Let's take care of ourselves.
ちゃんと気をもぐろう
yes.
はい
Can you wait one more time?
もう一回待てる?
Enough?
もういいや?
Do you not like it?
嫌なの?
Do you really hate it?
本当に嫌なの?
Which one?
どっち?
Shall we go again?
もう一回行こうか
With Sulis?
スリスと?
No, no.
ダメ、ダメ
Ozaki, give Beira a kiss.
小崎、ベイラちゃんにキスしてあげろよ
Hey, why don't you kiss me?
ほ ら、キスしてごらん?
Isn't it not strong enough?
力足りないんじゃない?
That's a stupid par.
バカいパーですね
Does that mean I can afford to kiss you?
キスできる余裕があるってこと?
I can't finish without opening my legs.
足開けなく終わんないよ
Isn't it over?
終わんない?
I'll give it another hour.
あと1時間当てるよ
Hey.
ねえ
He told me to keep my legs open for an hour.
足 開けなく1時間当てるよって
Please wait a moment.
ちょっと待ってください
What happened?
どうしちゃったの?
Everything is a little weak.
全部ちょっと弱いです
Was everything good?
全部よかった?
But I'll stop everything.
でも全部やめてあげるよ
Hey.
ね え
After this, it's a recent move.
この後最近の手だからね
Well then, let's lick Kozaki's dick for a bit.
じゃあ、ちょっと小崎のチンチン舐めよっか
Shall we practice pheran?
フェランを練習しよっか
copper?
どう?
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
I don't watch it all.
全部見ないですよ
Are there negotiations?
交渉なってる?
This is a negotiation.
交渉なってるよ、これ
It's a sensitivity check.
感度チェックだからね
I'm going to have my mom run around like a flying fish.
お母さんに もう、トビウオのように行きまくってもらっちゃう
Can you say that?
って 言える?
Dad, do you know how to lick?
お父さん、舐め方わかる?
It's so cute.
めっちゃ可愛いやん
Change, you.
変われよ、お前
I wish it was this cute.
こんな可愛かったらな
Changed me
変 われ
Yo.
よ
The time with Hitobura-san was more interesting.
ひ とぶらさんの時の方が面白い
It's so cute.
めっちゃ可愛いね
It feels great.
大気持ちいい
Where did you want to teach?
どこで教えたかった?
See how I lick it?
舐め方見してごらん?
That's amazing.
すごいね
I can't stand this.
たまらんやんな、これ
Move.
動いて
I told you, but you, please tell me.
教えたけど、お前、教えて
Are you licking it on the verge?
寸前で舐めてる?
On the verge?
寸前?
father
お 父
Mr. Sera is good.
さん、 セラうまいよ
It's okay, I didn't hear any calls from behind.
大丈夫だよ、後ろから電話ってないから
It would be terrible if you could guess this.
これ当てられたらやばいでしょ
It's better to be a phone than a finger.
指より電話になった方がいいよ
That's amazing.
すごいじゃん
What do you think?
どうなの?
It's not enough at all
全然足りてないです
Yo.
よ
Did you learn that by eating with your own hands?
そんな 手食いとこで覚えた?
That's too English.
英語すぎだろ
I like it.
好きだし
Do you like bags?
バック好きなの?
Do you want to add cheese to the back?
後ろ顔チーズ入れたいよか?
I'm glad.
喜んでんじゃん
Have you ever tried sunpee?
サンピーしたことある?
Maybe later?
後でしょっか
I might be lying if I say that.
俺が言ったら嘘かも
You don't understand, do you?
わかんないでしょ
I can tell you one thing, but my shop...
一つ言うのもすればいいけどさ、 うちのお店、
Actual performance.
本番
Are you okay?
大丈夫なんですか?
picture?
え?
What?
何が?
Actual performance.
本番
It's really okay.
ほんま大丈夫だよ
My shop is okay.
うちのお店、オッケーなんだよ
Yeah.
うん
Got it?
分かった?
All the customers will be angry.
お客さんの全員の中は怒るから
Shall I put it in then?
じゃあ入れよっか
I'll put it in raw.
生で入れちゃうよ
It's okay, it's okay.
大丈夫、大丈夫
It's okay.
だいじょうぶ
I'm being tested for STDs.
性病検査してるから
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
It feels good, right?
気持ちいいでしょ
Come over here.
こっち向いてこら
Okay.
いい よ
Follow me well.
上手くついてやれ
No, no, no.
ダメ、ダメ、ダメ
Just in case, just in case, just in case.
一 応、一応、一応
go.
行く
Go, go, go.
行く、行く、行く
Oh, no, no, no.
あぁ、だめ、だめ、だめ
I'm gone, I'm gone.
行っちゃった、行っちゃった
It's easy to wear.
着やすいんだね
It's best if you get to the window.
窓辺についたら良く
Do your best and fix it.
上手く、直してやれ
Oh, no, no, no.
あぁ、ダメ、ダメ、ダメ
Not yet, not yet, not yet.
まだ、まだ、まだ、 ダ メ、
No, no.
ダ メ、ダメ
Are you saying that?
そんな言っちゃうの?
It's not over yet?
まだ終わんないよ?
It's only been a minute, right?
まだ1分しかついてないよ?
It's okay to say otaki
おうたき言ったらいい
Yo.
よ
Acting?
演 技?
Are you serious about it?
ガチによっちゃう?
For real.
ガチに
It feels so good.
そんな気持ちいいんだよ
Good for you, Joker.
よかった、ジョーカーさん
He has a nice dick.
いいチンコ持ってるんだなぁ
It's coming.
来ますね
Follow me more, Otaki.
もっとついてやれ、おうたき
Layla, look here.
レイラちゃん、こっち見て
How about I give you more?
もっといっぱいついてあげたら?
I'll say it again.
また言っちゃう
what up?
どうした?
Did you come too?
お前も来たのか?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
Go, go, go, go.
行く、行く、行く、行く
I'm gone, I'm gone.
行っちゃった、行っちゃった
Leila-chan looks really happy.
レイラちゃん、めっちゃ嬉しそうじゃん
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
terrible.
やばい
go.
行く
It feels good, right?
気持ちいいでしょ
Layla-chan, can you move as you like?
レイラちゃん、もっと好きなように動いていい?
Yeah.
うん
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
I'll go again.
また行く
Go, go, go, no.
行く、行く、行く、ダメ
It's no good if you stop at your waist.
腰止めてはダメじゃん
I have to go there again and again.
何度も行っちゃわないと、ほら
For real.
ガチに
I'll go again.
また行く
Long live Leila-chan.
レイラちゃん、万歳してほら
oh yeah
そうそう
yes.
そう
Ah, amazing.
あ、 すごい
sorry.
ごめん
I'll go again.
また行っちゃう
Ah, let's go.
あ、行っちゃう
There's matcha out there.
抹茶出ちゃってるじゃん
That's too much to pay for.
報酬で出すすぎだよね
That's no good.
ダメじゃん
You made a great baby.
すごい赤ちゃん出来ちゃったね
Le Ira-chan, look at the letter A.
レ イラちゃん、ちょっとA文字になってほら
With the letter A, yeah yeah yeah.
A文字で、そうそうそう
The inside is standard, and both pieces are pieces.
内側が定番して、両方でピースして、
There.
そこで
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Look here.
こっち見て
I'll take a photo of this.
これ写真撮っとくからね
Got it?
分かった?
Yes, peace.
はい、ピースして
Did something happen to this?
これ何かあった?
This is from pieces.
これバラバラから
Got it?
分かった?
When I said I was quitting the shop, all of these photos were taken apart.
お店やめるって言ったら、この写真バラバラからね
Just kidding.
冗談だよ
I'll give you this for the Photo Menu machine later.
後で写メニュー機用にこれあげるから
Well then, Leila-chan, let's take a bath.
じゃあレイラちゃん、お風呂入ろっか
Shower beat event.
シャワービートイベント
There are experiential exhibits.
体験の展示があるからね
Take care.
いってらっしゃい